myblogtips.org 2015-03-20

# Privacy Policy | Blogger Tips and Tricks

Myblogtips is a blogging community where all bloggers submit their latest blog articles, video tutorials  for increasing backlinks and traffic.

Your access to and use of this website is subject to these Terms and Conditions. You will not use the Website for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these Terms and Conditions. By using the Website you are fully accepting this websites the terms, conditions and disclaimers contained in this notice. If you do not accept these Terms and Conditions you must immediately stop using the Website.  
We Will send you mass e-mail announcements from our community regarding upgrades and updates, sales and special offers. We will not sell your e-mail or private information. When adding content to your PUBLIC profile users within the PUBLIC may have access to it by visiting your PUBLIC profile.  
Myblogtips has all the right to delete, remove, cancel your account at anytime without sending any notice if you are violate the sites rules. We do not allow porno of abusive content to be submitted to our community.  
This Website may include links to third party websites that are controlled and maintained by others. Any link to other websites is not an endorsement of such websites and you acknowledge and agree that we are not responsible for the content or availability of any such sites. 

**  **  
**Privacy Policy for www.myblogtips.org**  

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at kbloggertemplates@gmail.com. 

At www.myblogtips.org, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.myblogtips.org and how it is used. 

###  **Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, www.myblogtips.org makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

###  Cookies and Web Beacons ** **

www.myblogtips.org does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

###  DoubleClick DART Cookie ** **

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.myblogtips.org.  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.myblogtips.org and other sites on the Internet.   
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....  
Google Adsense

Adbrite

chitika 

Infolinks

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.myblogtips.org send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

www.myblogtips.org has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.myblogtips.org's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
